Guide to the Outdoor Advertising Association of America Slide Library, 1891-2000 and undated RL.00965
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Award Nominees Series, 1965-1968, 1983-1987 and undated
  While a sizable series, only a relatively small portion of many decades of national competition nominees are represented here. It has not been determined with certainty whether the outdoor industry sponsored any awards from 1973 to 1982, but the OBIE award was not awarded during that time. This may explain most of the gap in slides from 1969 through 1982. Some transparencies also are included in this series. Labeled yellow slips were found attached to original slide sleeves, perhaps referring to slides removed at one point. Information on these slips was transferred to acid-free paper and clipped to the new archival sleeve. Some images are marked as being winners in a particular category, but most slides or sleeves have no such marking. Old notebook designations (A-1, A-2...) were maintained on the slide sleeves. Old notebooks were listed in the preliminary boxlist as follows: A-1: 33rd-35th National Competition (1965-1967); A-2: 1984; A-3: 1984; A-4: 1985; A-5: 1985; A-6: 1986; A-7: 1986; A-8: 1986; A-9: 1987; A-10: 1987; A-11: 1987; A-12: Various Designs and Awards. Hard copies of old boxlists may be found in this repository's inventory drawers.
  Slides are arranged by award competition dates and were numbered in that order, all with the prefix "SLA." In this series only, slides inserted after most had already been numbered were assigned a number with an alphabetical suffix so all slides following would not have to be renumbered.
  Online Items
  Some items from this collection have been digitized and described in: Resource of Outdoor Advertising Descriptions (ROAD)
  - 1965: 33rd National Competition of Outdoor Advertising Art (Box AW1)
    - SLA0001-SLA0086 (Box AW1)
  - 1966: 34th National Competition of Outdoor Advertising Art
    - SLA0087-SLA0164 (Box AW1)
  - 1967: 35th National Competition of Outdoor Advertising Art
    - SLA0165-SLA0261 (Box AW1)
  - 1968: 36th Outdoor Advertising Competition
    - SLA0262-SLA0277 (Box AW1)
  - 1983/84: OBIE Award Competition
    - SLA0278-SLA0327 (Box AW1)
  - 1983/84: OBIE Award Competition (Box AW2)
    - SLA0328-SLA0824(A-J) (Box AW2)
  - 1985: OBIE Award Competition (Box AW3)
    - SLA0825-SLA1469 (Box AW3)
  - 1985: OBIE Award Competition (Box AW4)
    - SLA1470-SLA1524 (Box AW4)
  - 1985/86: OBIE Award Competition
    - SLA1525-SLA2046 (Box AW4)
  - 1985/86: OBIE Award Competition (Box AW5)
    - SLA2047-SLA2545(A-L) (Box AW5)
  - 1986/87: OBIE Award Competition
    - SLA2546-SLA2677 (Box AW5)
  - 1986/87: OBIE Award Competition (Box AW6)
    - SLA2678-SLA3279(A-L) (Box AW6)
  - 1986/87: OBIE Award Competition (Box AW7)
    - SLA3280-SLA3575 (Box AW7)
  - Miscellaneous Nominees
    - SLA3576-SLA3975 (Box AW7)
- Chronological Series, 1891-1994 and undated
  The Chronological Series slides ("SLD" and "SLG" slides) are roughly in chronological order within each box. The earlier images have a higher concentration of poster advertisements as opposed to billboards. The series is almost completely made up of advertisement slides, but there are also some street scenes and a few other slides that could be tied to a specific era.
  - 1891-1950 (Box CH1)
    - SLD0001-SLD0740 (Box CH1)
  - 1946-1957 (Box CH2)
    - SLD0741-SLD1420 (Box CH2)
  - 1950-1960s (Box CH3)
    - SLD1421-SLD2100 (Box CH3)
  - 1951-1956 (Box CH4)
    - SLD2101-SLD2860 (Box CH4)
  - 1951-1960 (Box CH5)
    - SLD2861-SLD3660 (Box CH5)
  - 1952-1960 (Box CH6)
    - SLD3661-SLD4520 (Box CH6)
  - 1955-1962 (Box CH7)
    - SLD4521-SLD5440 (Box CH7)
  - 1950-1962 (Box CH8)
    - SLD5441-SLD6240 (Box CH8)
  - 1960-1963 (Box CH9)
    - SLD6241-SLD7080 (Box CH9)
  - 1961-1963 (Box CH10)
    - SLD7081-SLD7780 (Box CH10)
  - 1959-1963 (Box CH11)
    - SLD7781-SLD8620 (Box CH11)
  - 1961-1964 (Box CH12)
    - SLD8621-SLD9460 (Box CH12)
  - 1964 (Box CH13)
    - SLD9461-SLD9999 (Box CH13)
    - SLG0001-SLG0281 (Box CH13)
  - 1964-1965 (Box CH14)
    - SLG0282-SLG1096 (Box CH14)
  - 1965-1970 (Box CH15)
    - SLG1097-SLG1777 (Box CH15)
  - 1965-1970 (Box CH16)
    - SLG1781-SLG2520 (Box CH16)
  - 1966-1984(no slides for the date span 1976-1983) (Box CH17)
    - SLG2521-SLG3380 (Box CH17)
  - 1971-1989(no slides for the date span 1986-1988) (Box CH18)
    - SLG3381-SLG4160 (Box CH18)
  - 1981-1987 (Box CH19)
    - SLG4161-SLG4860 (Box CH19)
  - 1987-1988 (Box CH20)
    - SLG4861-SLG5520 (Box CH20)
  - 1988-1989 (Box CH21)
    - SLG5521-SLG6400 (Box CH21)
  - 1989-1990 (Box CH22)
    - SLG6401-SLG7300 (Box CH22)
  - 1990-1992 (Box CH23)
    - SLG7301-SLG8280 (Box CH23)
  - 1992-1993 (Box CH24)
    - SLG8281-SLG9180 (Box CH24)
  - 1993-1994 (Box CH25)
    - SLG9181-SLG9880 (Box CH25)
- Topical Series, undated
  The Topical Series is the largest group of advertisement slides in the collection and is organized by product or service type. It has been maintained in two separate but similar subseries, the second being the larger of the two. To provide meaningful organizational categories for sometimes vague products, issues, and services, each category within each subseries is in effect one of three things, (1) a product type (food, cars, etc.), (2) a sponsoring organization (armed forces, liquor stores, etc.), or (3) an ad type (public service, political ads, etc.). Read through the entire list to target a search before browsing through boxes. Advertisements are often arranged into subgroups and then alphabetically by brand name within the groups listed below. For the second subseries, see category descriptions appended to this document before searching. A large percentage of the slides are undated but range from at least 1940 through 1988. There are probably earlier images in this series as well that could not be dated precisely.
  - Subseries I
    Arrangement note
    The first subseries (Subseries I, "SLP" and "SLQ" slides) is roughly organized into groups according to product types listed below. Some of the Miscellaneous groupings are extensive and should be consulted in a comprehensive search. These slides have been maintained in their original order. Topics may appear in more than one box.
    - SLP0001-SLP0740 (Box TP1)
      - US Armed Forces (Box TP1)
      - Boys Scouts (Box TP1)
      - Ad Council, Public Service (Box TP1)
      - Alcoholic Beverages (non-beer) (Box TP1)
    - SLP0741-SLP1540 (Box TP2)
      - Alcoholic Beverages (non-beer) continued (Box TP2)
      - Liquor Stores (Box TP2)
      - Beer (roughly in alphabetical order by brand name)
        - A-Falstaff (Box TP2)
    - SLP1541-SLP2360 (Box TP3)
      - Beer continued
        - Falstaff - Pearl (Box TP3)
    - SLP2361-SLP3140 (Box TP4)
      - Beer continued
        - Pearl - Wiedemann's (Box TP4)
        - Miscellaneous brands (Box TP4)
    - SLP3141-SLP3840 (Box TP5)
      - Beer continued
        - Miscellaneous brands (Box TP5)
      - Alcoholic Beverages (non-beer) (Box TP5)
      - Automotive/Motorcycles (roughly in alphabetical order by manufacturer/dealer)
        - American Motors - Ford (Box TP5)
    - SLP3841-SLP4600 (Box TP6)
      - Automotive/Motorcycles continued
        - Ford - Honda (Box TP6)
        - Miscellaneous (Box TP6)
        - Hyundai - Yugo (Box TP6)
        - Miscellaneous (Box TP6)
    - SLP4601-SLP5180 (Box TP7)
      - Automotive/Motorcycles continued
        - Car Parts and Service (Box TP7)
        - Tires (Box TP7)
        - Car Parts (Box TP7)
        - Car Rental (Box TP7)
      - Financial Services (primarily banks/insurance roughly in alphabetical order)
        - Ahmanson Mortgage - First National Bank (Box TP7)
    - SLP5181-SLP5780 (Box TP8)
      - Financial Services continued
        - First National Bank - Pittsburgh National (Box TP8)
        - Watertown - Zions (Box TP8)
        - Pittsburgh National - Zions (Box TP8)
        - Credit Cards (Box TP8)
        - Miscellaneous financial (Box TP8)
      - Non-alcoholic Beverages (esp. soft drinks including mixers; roughly in alphabetical order)
        - AandW - Coca-Cola (Box TP8)
    - SLP5781-SLP6460 (Box TP9)
      - Non-alcoholic Beverages continued
        - Coca-Cola - 7-Up (Box TP9)
        - Miscellaneous (Box TP9)
        - Juice and Coffee (Box TP9)
      - Tobacco (primarily cigarettes roughly in alphabetical order)
        - Basic - Kent (Box TP9)
    - SLP6461-SLP7080 (Box TP10)
      - Tobacco continued
        - Kent - Winston (Box TP10)
      - Amusement Parks/Farms (Box TP10)
      - Books (Box TP10)
      - Miscellaneous (especially products pertaining to entertainment including publications, gasoline, casinos, electronics, retail, alcohol, books, record albums, television shows, celebrity/concert appearances, movies, mouthwash, circuses, fairs, miniature golf, lottery, magazines, museums, and symphonies) (Box TP10)
      - Newspapers (Box TP10)
      - Pet Shops (Box TP10)
      - Animal Parks/Exhibits (Box TP10)
      - Sporting Goods, Events, and Teams (Box TP10)
      - Playhouses, Studios, and Zoos (Box TP10)
      - Movies (Box TP10)
      - Radio and Television Stations/Shows (Box TP10)
    - SLP7081-SLP7700 (Box TP11)
      - Radio and Television Stations/Shows continued (Box TP11)
      - Pet/Animal Feed (Box TP11)
      - Food
        - Bakery Items (Box TP11)
        - Bread (Box TP11)
        - Butter (Box TP11)
        - Buttermilk (Box TP11)
        - Candy, Snacks, and Gum (Box TP11)
    - SLP7701-SLP8320 (Box TP12)
      - Food continued
        - Candy, Snacks, and Gum (Box TP12)
        - Cereal and Breakfast Foods (Box TP12)
        - Cheese Products (Box TP12)
        - Eggs (Box TP12)
        - Flour (Box TP12)
        - Fruit (Box TP12)
        - Ice Cream and Popsicles (Box TP12)
        - Jelly and Baby Food (Box TP12)
        - Ketchup (catsup) (Box TP12)
        - Margarine (Box TP12)
        - Mayonnaise (Box TP12)
        - Meat, Fish Products, and Rice (Box TP12)
    - SLP8321-SLP9040 (Box TP13)
      - Food continued
        - Meat, Fish Products, and Rice (Box TP13)
        - Milk/Dairy Products (Box TP13)
        - Mustard (Box TP13)
        - Nuts (Box TP13)
        - Peanut butter (Box TP13)
        - Pickles (Box TP13)
        - Potato Chips, Crackers, and Snack Foods (Box TP13)
        - Salad Dressing (Box TP13)
        - Potato Chips (Box TP13)
        - Salt (Box TP13)
        - Sour Cream (Box TP13)
        - Sugar (Box TP13)
    - SLP9041-SLP9660 (Box TP14)
      - Food continued
        - Sugar (Box TP14)
        - Vegetables (Box TP14)
        - Jell-O Products (Box TP14)
        - Heinz Products (Box TP14)
        - Shortening (Box TP14)
        - Miscellaneous (Box TP14)
      - Aluminum Foil (Box TP14)
      - Gasoline and Automotive (primarily gasoline/oil; roughly alphabetical by brand; includes some auto parts and service)
        - Amoco - Hancock (Box TP14)
    - SLP9661-SLP9999 (Box TP15)
      - Gasoline and Automotive continued
        - Hancock - Shell (Box TP15)
    - SLQ0001-SLQ0300
      - Gasoline and Automotive continued
        - Shell - Signal (Box TP15)
    - SLQ0301-SLQ1000 (Box TP16)
      - Gasoline and Automotive continued
        - Shell - Union 76 (includes Standard/Chevron) (Box TP16)
        - Miscellaneous (Box TP16)
      - Pain and Cold Medicine (Box TP16)
      - Oral/Personal Hygiene (Box TP16)
      - Eyewear (Box TP16)
      - Hair and Skin Products (Box TP16)
      - Dental and Medical (Box TP16)
      - Miscellaneous Personal Products and Retail (Includes medicines, bath, health, and beauty products, pharmacies, beauty salons, and sunscreen) (Box TP16)
    - SLQ1001-SLQ1620 (Box TP17)
      - Miscellaneous Personal Products and Retail continued (Box TP17)
      - Restaurants (roughly alphabetical)
        - Acapulco - Der Wienerschnitzel (Box TP17)
        - Ice Cream Shops (Box TP17)
        - Allenhurst - Zim's (Box TP17)
      - Apparel, Apparel Stores and other Retail (roughly alphabetical; includes some watches, cosmetics, electronics, shopping centers, and other department store consumer goods purchases)
        - Anell's - Robinson's (Box TP17)
    - SLQ1621-SLQ2320 (Box TP18)
      - Apparel, Apparel Stores, and other Retail continued
        - Robinson's - Zayre (Box TP18)
        - Miscellaneous (Box TP18)
        - Footwear (Box TP18)
        - Miscellaneous (Box TP18)
      - Grocery Stores (roughly in alphabetical order)
        - AG Stores - Winn Dixie (Box TP18)
      - Airlines (roughly in alphabetical order)
        - Alaska Airlines - Western Airlines (Box TP18)
    - SLQ2321-SLQ2980 (Box TP19)
      - Airlines continued
        - Western Airlines - World Airways (Box TP19)
      - Transportation and Travel (Includes public transportation, bicycles, mopeds, travel agencies, cruises, vacation destinations, commerce/convention destinations, resorts, miscellaneous attractions, and shopping centers) (Box TP19)
      - Hotels (Box TP19)
      - Moving and Storage (Box TP19)
      - Utility Companies (often ads featuring appliances) (Box TP19)
      - Heating and Air Conditioning (Box TP19)
      - Electronics and Appliances (Box TP19)
      - Photographic Equipment (Box TP19)
      - Laundry Detergent and Dry Cleaning (Box TP19)
      - Household Cleaners (Box TP19)
      - Hosiery, Footwear, and Apparel (Box TP19)
      - Florists (Box TP19)
    - SLQ2981-SLQ3597 (Box TP20)
      - Florists continued (Box TP20)
      - Construction and Home Improvement (Includes building materials, floor and wall coverings, decorators, furniture stores, and mattresses) (Box TP20)
      - Insurance (Box TP20)
      - Lawn Care (Box TP20)
      - Metals (Includes Aluminum, Steel Buildings) (Box TP20)
      - Data Processing and Printers (Box TP20)
      - Paper Products (Includes napkins, tissues, wax paper, and toilet tissue) (Box TP20)
      - Paint (Box TP20)
      - Plumbing (Box TP20)
      - Political Ads (Box TP20)
      - Real Estate (Box TP20)
      - Campers (Box TP20)
      - Miscellaneous (Includes massage school, zippers, and trading stamps) (Box TP20)
      - Yellow Pages (Box TP20)
  - Subseries II
    These slides were grouped into industry standard categories. Please see category descriptions at the end of this document to facilitate your search. Often, like materials are further grouped within these categories. For ads where identity of the product was unclear, a small Product Unclear category was created at the end of this subseries. This subseries contains slide numbers with the following prefixes: SLS, SLT, SLU, SLV, SLW, SLX, SLY, SLZ, SLJ, SLK, and SLL.
    - Apparel (Box TP21)
      - SLS0001-SLS0274 (Box TP21)
    - Retail
      - SLS0275-SLS0693 (Box TP21)
    - Retail (Box TP22)
      - SLS0694-SLS1353 (Box TP22)
    - Retail (Box TP23)
      - SLS1354-SLS1413 (Box TP23)
    - Retail / Apparel
      - SLS1414-SLS1649 (Box TP23)
    - Business and Technology
      - SLT0001-SLT0280 (Box TP23)
    - Business and Technology (Box TP24)
      - SLT0281-SLT0980 (Box TP24)
    - Business and Technology (Box TP25)
      - SLT0981-SLT1640 (Box TP25)
    - Business and Technology (Box TP26)
      - SLT1641-SLT2340 (Box TP26)
    - Business and Technology (Box TP27)
      - SLT2341-SLT2754 (Box TP27)
    - Amusement and Entertainment
      - SLU0001-SLU0140 (Box TP27)
    - Amusement and Entertainment (Box TP28)
      - SLU0141-SLU0820 (Box TP28)
    - Transportation and Travel (Box TP29)
      - SLV0001-SLV0500 (Box TP29)
    - Transportation and Travel (Box TP30)
      - SLV0501-SLV1200 (Box TP30)
    - Transportation and Travel (Box TP31)
      - SLV1201-SLV1526 (Box TP31)
    - Automotive
      - SLW0001-SLW0280 (Box TP31)
    - Automotive (Box TP32)
      - SLW0281-SLW0980 (Box TP32)
    - Automotive (Box TP33)
      - SLW0981-SLW1620 (Box TP33)
    - Automotive (Box TP34)
      - SLW1621-SLW1845 (Box TP34)
    - Consumer Goods and Services
      - SLX0001-SLX0380 (Box TP34)
    - Consumer Goods and Services (Box TP35)
      - SLX0381-SLX1020 (Box TP35)
    - Consumer Goods and Services (Box TP36)
      - SLX1021-SLX1660 (Box TP36)
    - Consumer Goods and Services (Box TP37)
      - SLX1661-SLX2072 (Box TP37)
    - Beverages
      - SLY0001-SLY0080 (Box TP37)
    - Beverages (Box TP38)
      - SLY0081-SLY0560 (Box TP38)
    - Beverages (Box TP39)
      - SLY0561-SLY1020 (Box TP39)
    - Beverages (Box TP40)
      - SLY1021-SLY1427 (Box TP40)
    - Beverages (Box TP41)
      - SLY1428-SLY1947 (Box TP41)
    - Beverages (Box TP42)
      - SLY1948-SLY2467 (Box TP42)
    - Beverages (Box TP43)
      - SLY2468-SLY2967 (Box TP43)
    - Beverages (Box TP44)
      - SLY2968-SLY3332 (Box TP44)
    - Food and Restaurants
      - SLZ0001-SLZ0100 (Box TP44)
    - Food and Restaurants (Box TP45)
      - SLZ0101-SLZ0720 (Box TP45)
    - Food and Restaurants (Box TP46)
      - SLZ0721-SLZ1375 (Box TP46)
    - Public Service (Box TP47)
      - SLJ0001-SLJ0544 (Box TP47)
    - Media (Box TP48)
      - SLK0001-SLK0660 (Box TP48)
    - Media (Box TP49)
      - SLK0661-SLK1113 (Box TP49)
    - Product Unclear
      - SLL0001-SLL0117 (Box TP49)
- International Posters Series, 1925-1983, bulk mid-late 1960s, especially 1969
  Presumably, some of the ads in this series ("SLM" slides) were submitted for an International category of the OBIE awards program, a category added in more recent years. They are often in a smaller poster format to accommodate larger pedestrian audiences abroad. Some products featured include alcoholic beverages, concerts, cheese, travel, London transportation, beverages, museum exhibitions, festivals, ice cream, newspapers, and the Moscow Olympics. The slides are arranged by slide number.
  Existence and Location of Copies note
  Some items from this series have been digitized and described in: Resource of Outdoor Advertising Descriptions (ROAD)
  - SLM0001-SLM0621 (Box TT1)
- Construction and Creation Series, 1950s-1980s and undated
  This small series ("SLE" slides) provides perhaps the most context for the creative process. More than just the finished product, these slide images show ads at every stage of creation from idea boards to finishing touches. Most slides show images of people working on billboards, but there are also graphics showing billboard dimensions or various billboard types, photo images of workrooms, workers at worktables, workers with equipment doing actual construction, cranes hanging large billboard segments, photos of props used to put together an image, shots of billboards at various stages of completion, close shots of trim pieces, and more. The slides are arranged by slide number.
  - SLE0001-SLE0135 (Box TT2)
- Artwork Series, 1956-1973 and undated
  This series contains slide images of original artwork ("SLF" slides), usually not in any advertisement format. Artwork was sometimes submitted to OAAA as part of the OBIE Awards program. Many of these slides are labeled with the artist's name such as graphic artist and painter, Luis Gordillo. Other names found in this part of the collection include Eric Lanneau, Luis Perez Minguez, T. Mixta, Boix, A. Heras, E. Borduas, Robert Burns, F.C.B. Cadell, R. McG. Coventry, G.D. Davison, John Duncan, Crawhall, George Henry, J.W. Herald, Hornel, Leslie Hunter, W.Y. MacGregor, J.Q. Pringle, Claude Breeze, Ivan Eyre, Alex Coville, and Opura Benazon. Slides are arranged by slide number.
  - SLF0001-SLF0208 (Box TT2)
- Street Scenes and Approaches Series, 1930s-1980s and undated
  This series ("SLH" slides) contains slides with images of street scenes, often showing long approaches to billboard sites. There are examples of outdoor advertising present, but views are from a distance. These images were used in planning and preparation for construction or to show sites to prospective clients. This series reveals the most outdoor context of time and place for the advertising. While most shots in other series are close-ups of billboards, these photo images almost always show a wider scene. Slides are arranged by slide number.
  - SLH0001-0131 (Box TT2)
- Other Outdoor Advertising Related Images Series, ca. 1910-1985 and undated
  This small series ("SLN" slides) contains slides with images that did not easily fit into other categories. It includes slides of the 1975 Miss America and other campaigns designed to test or prove how well people could remember information from the outdoor medium. Various pieces of art are included, as well as a mock-up of a Signs of the Times publication cover; photographs related to a consumer survey; group portraits from industry meetings, some from as early as the 1910s; print advertisements; and portraits of advertising executives including Burr Robbins. Slides are arranged by slide number.
  - SLN0001-SLN0091 (Box TT2)
- Presentations and Presentation Slides Series, 1960s-1980s and undated
  This series contains slides organized for individual presentations, several with scripts included. The presentations at the start of the series are the most complete. As the list continues, the presentations become less complete (e.g. lacking slides, transcripts, etc.), until only loose slides from presentations are present. The intact presentations at the start of the series were created for a variety of audiences by outdoor executives often as training devices or sales tools for prospective clients. A number of the presentations were put together by the Institute of Outdoor Advertising, the marketing arm of the industry. The scripts and slides provide a mix of information not found in other series, including an introduction to the medium, comparisons to other advertising media, and history of the industry.
  Included are some historical images from the early days of outdoor advertising, but the series mostly contains mid to late 20th century images including billboard construction; shots of the creative process; labeled charts indicating the standard billboard sizes; statistics on cost, reach, frequency, and readership; and much more information about the medium in general. Though not indexed in the ROAD database, there are many images of outdoor advertising used as examples in the presentations. Some slides relate to specific companies or campaigns such as Kraft, specific markets such as Birmingham, or certain product types such as insurance or magazines. Many of the loose slides are grouped into at least partial presentations. Three of the scripted presentations have audiocassette recordings included in box PR13. There are duplicate slides in some presentations and so presumably, many were created and used in various presentations according to the need at the time. For database control purposes, individual "SLB" numbers were assigned to whole presentations.
  - Presentations: (Box PR1)
    - Outdoor Goes to College (SLB0001) (Box PR1)
      Audio recording of script included in box PR13.
    - It Pays to be Creative (Institute of Outdoor Advertising [IOA]) (SLB0002) (Box PR1)
      This presentation is aimed at new creative directors and discusses among other things what makes a good design and how to sell it. Audio recording of script included in box PR13.
    - Media Insurance (IOA) (SLB0003), 3 folders (Box PR1)
      This presentation seems designed to sell the medium to potential advertisers. Audio recording of script included in box PR13.
    - Profiles of Outdoor Advertising Readers (Outdoor Advertising Incorporated [OAI]) (SLB0004) (Box PR2)
    - Working Women (Donnelly Adv.) (SLB0005) (Box PR2)
    - Be It Ever So Humble, There?s No Place Like Out-of-Home (IOA) (SLB0006) (Box PR2)
    - A Presentation on Geometrics (Center for Advertising Services, 1976) (SLB0007) (Box PR2)
    - Dialogue Presentation (IOA) (SLB0008) (Box PR2)
    - The Giant (IOA) (SLB0009) (Box PR2)
    - Outdoor for Retailers (SLB0010) (Box PR2)
    - Kraft (SLB0011) (Box PR2)